[
  {
    "question": "1 + 1 = _",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "A, E, I, O, _",
    "answer": "U"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 9 = _",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bube, Dame, KÃ¶nig, _",
    "answer": "Ass"
  },
  {
    "question": "1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, _",
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "MDMDFS_",
    "answer": "Sonntag"
  },
  {
    "question": "A=3, B=3, C=1, D=2, E=4, F=_",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kevin, Stuart, _",
    "answer": "Bob"
  },
  {
    "question": "PTUXJOE",
    "answer": "Ostwind"
  },
  {
    "question": "T.S., R.D., A.J., F.S., P.P., R.",
    "answer": "Equestria"
  },
  {
    "question": "???",
    "answer": "Hitchcock"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rgl",
    "answer": "iee"
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 8 = 3, 21 + 5 = 2, 14 + 1 = 15, 22 + 7 = _",
    "answer": "5"
  }
]
